[{"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["4+4", "1+5", "9-6", "2+0", "3+5", "4+5", "9-8", "3+6", "4+0", "7-6", "1+3", "1+0"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["4+4", "1+5", "3+5", "4+5", "3+6"], ["9-6", "2+0", "9-8", "4+0"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["7-6", "5-4", "2+2", "8-6", "5-3", "4-1", "2+7", "3+0", "1+0", "2+6", "3+3", "3+5"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["2+7", "2+6", "3+3", "3+5"], ["7-6", "5-4", "2+2", "8-6", "5-3"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["2+1", "9-6", "9-3", "1+0", "5-4", "3+5", "2+7", "7-6", "2+2", "1+3", "3+6", "5-3"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["9-3", "3+5", "2+7", "3+6"], ["2+1", "9-6", "1+0", "5-4", "7-6"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["7-6", "2+1", "5-3", "4+0", "9-3", "3+1", "3+5", "8-6", "6-4", "3+0", "4+4", "9-8"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["9-3", "3+5", "4+4"], ["7-6", "2+1", "5-3", "4+0", "3+1", "8-6"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["9-6", "1+8", "2+2", "5-4", "3+5", "9-3", "1+7", "4+0", "2+1", "1+3", "4+5", "1+5"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["1+8", "3+5", "9-3", "1+7", "4+5", "1+5"], ["9-6", "2+2", "5-4"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["3+3", "7-6", "1+7", "9-6", "1+3", "3+6", "4+4", "8-6", "2+0", "2+7", "1+8", "4-1"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["3+3", "1+7", "3+6", "4+4", "2+7", "1+8"], ["7-6", "9-6", "1+3"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["2+1", "4+5", "2+0", "9-3", "2+2", "2+7", "6-4", "2+4", "7-6", "4+4", "8-6", "3+5"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["4+5", "9-3", "2+7", "2+4", "4+4", "3+5"], ["2+1", "2+0", "2+2"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["4+0", "4+4", "2+4", "1+7", "3+1", "4+5", "9-3", "3+5", "3+3", "9-6", "2+0", "1+3"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["4+4", "2+4", "1+7", "4+5", "9-3", "3+5", "3+3"], ["4+0", "3+1"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["9-3", "4+5", "7-6", "2+1", "4-1", "4+4", "3+1", "9-6", "3+5", "5-4", "2+4", "2+0"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["9-3", "4+5", "4+4", "3+5", "2+4"], ["7-6", "2+1", "4-1", "3+1"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["3+5", "4+0", "5-4", "2+7", "3+3", "1+8", "7-6", "9-8", "9-6", "4+4", "5-3", "9-3"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["3+5", "2+7", "3+3", "1+8", "4+4", "9-3"], ["4+0", "5-4", "7-6"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["4+0", "4+4", "2+6", "1+7", "2+1", "9-6", "6-4", "1+8", "9-8", "3+5", "2+0", "9-3"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["4+4", "2+6", "1+7", "1+8", "3+5", "9-3"], ["4+0", "2+1", "9-6"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["9-3", "4+4", "4+5", "2+0", "8-6", "1+5", "3+1", "1+0", "3+5", "4-1", "2+1", "5-3"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["9-3", "4+4", "4+5", "1+5", "3+5"], ["2+0", "8-6", "3+1", "1+0"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["3+5", "6-4", "5-4", "1+7", "1+5", "3+0", "9-3", "2+2", "7-6", "1+3", "4+0", "4-1"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["3+5", "1+7", "1+5", "9-3"], ["6-4", "5-4", "3+0", "2+2", "7-6"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["6-4", "2+2", "5-3", "1+5", "2+6", "1+8", "1+3", "9-6", "4+0", "9-3", "3+3", "1+0"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["1+5", "2+6", "1+8", "9-3", "3+3"], ["6-4", "2+2", "5-3", "1+3"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["3+0", "1+8", "3+1", "2+0", "1+5", "9-6", "3+3", "2+6", "4+4", "6-4", "2+2", "3+5"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["1+8", "1+5", "3+3", "2+6", "4+4", "3+5"], ["3+0", "3+1", "2+0"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["7-6", "3+5", "1+7", "2+2", "9-6", "4-1", "2+4", "1+8", "3+0", "1+0", "1+5", "8-6"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["3+5", "1+7", "2+4", "1+8", "1+5"], ["7-6", "2+2", "9-6", "4-1"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["1+7", "4+4", "5-4", "4-1", "3+5", "2+0", "1+3", "2+4", "2+7", "3+3", "5-3", "1+0"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["1+7", "4+4", "3+5", "2+4", "2+7", "3+3"], ["5-4", "4-1", "2+0"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类", "stem": "分类", "num": "5", "questionItem": ["2+6", "4+0", "5-3", "3+1", "9-6", "3+0", "3+3", "2+7", "9-8", "1+7", "1+0", "3+5"], "type": "au-equation-drag2"}], "answers": [["2+6", "3+3", "2+7", "1+7", "3+5"], ["4+0", "5-3", "3+1", "9-6"]], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-5"}]